SEYED MEHDI MAZHARI MOUSAVI

Senior Web Developer



mr.mazhari@gmail.com



(226) 246-8765



1400 Ouellette Ave Windsor, ON, N8X4T4

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Adaptable professional with 7.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of web platform development, search engine optimization, and server configuration. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Senior Web Developer role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer

Douglas Marketing Group, Windsor, ON / Mar 2019 - Present

- WordPress Web Developer: Programming more than 30 websites. Managing more than 70 websites.
- Full Stack Web Developer: Programming custom plugin, custom shortcodes, custom themes by using PHP, HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, Ajax, Json, API, and some third-party plugins like Advanced custom fields and Custom post types
- DevOps: Install two dedicated servers on AWS from scratch and using CentOS and WHM cPanel on it. Managing AWS, WHM, Security, and Load optimization.
- Search Engine Optimization: Using SEO Yoast plugin and new technologies and suggestions for SEO optimization. Using SEMrush for our clients to crawl and audit their SEO errors. Full understanding of Google ads, Tag Manager, Google analytics, and google search console.
- Security Specialist: Install integrated WordPress management like infinitewp. Work with security plugins like WordFence and all in one. Security optimizations and reduce vulnerabilities.
- Network and Server Manager: Install firewall Kerio for the office and set up all the traffic rules. Build solid HP server gen8 server with Proxmox Virtual Environment. Managing windows server 2019.

WordPress Online Tutor

Maktabkhooneh, Tehran, Tehran / Feb 2018 - Present

- Providing 10 hours training course of WordPress Essentials
- How to build a website?
- How to build a shop?
- · Hosting and launching a website.

Web Developer and IT Manager

Savanagroup, Behshahr, Mazandaran / Feb 2017 - Sep 2018

- WordPress developer. Managing multiple websites of holdings. Content developer.
- Network administrator and maintenance
- · Windows Server administrator
- SEO and Social media manager

Web Developer

Remakish, Tehran, Tehran / Sep 2015 - Jan 2016

- Develop multiple WordPress websites for the main company and representatives.
- Develop and optimize android app
- · Design and programming Office automation systems with ASP.NET

Web Developer

Information and Communities Technology Babol, Babol, Mazandaran / May 2013 - Nov 2013

· Design and programming E-Commerce Application

EDUCATION

AZAD UNIVERSITY OF GARMSAR GPA: 3.65 Garmsar, Semnan Master of Science (M.S.) Computer Networking (Oct 2016)

UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY BABOL GPA: 3.05 Babol, Mazandaran Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Information Technology (Dec 2013)